{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of esports with this quiz.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which game features Dust II?",
      "answers": ["CS:GO", "Dota 2", "LoL"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has Summoner's Rift?",
      "answers": ["LoL", "Overwatch", "CS:GO"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Faker known for?",
      "answers": ["LoL", "Dota 2", "CS:GO"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has The International?",
      "answers": ["Dota 2", "LoL", "Overwatch"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has deagle?",
      "answers": ["CS:GO", "LoL", "Dota 2"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Ninja known for?",
      "answers": ["Fortnite", "LoL", "Dota 2"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has AWP?",
      "answers": ["CS:GO", "Dota 2", "LoL"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game features Reinhardt?",
      "answers": ["Overwatch", "LoL", "CS:GO"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has Dragonblade?",
      "answers": ["Overwatch", "Dota 2", "LoL"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has Radiant?",
      "answers": ["Valorant", "LoL", "Dota 2"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has Nuke?",
      "answers": ["CS:GO", "LoL", "Overwatch"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has Rekkles?",
      "answers": ["LoL", "Dota 2", "CS:GO"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has Aim Lab?",
      "answers": ["Valorant", "LoL", "Dota 2"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has Dustbowl?",
      "answers": ["TF2", "Overwatch", "CS:GO"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has Bounty Runes?",
      "answers": ["Dota 2", "LoL", "CS:GO"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has Mirage?",
      "answers": ["CS:GO", "Overwatch", "Dota 2"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has MidOne?",
      "answers": ["Dota 2", "LoL", "CS:GO"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has Bind?",
      "answers": ["Valorant", "LoL", "Dota 2"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has MOBA?",
      "answers": ["LoL", "CS:GO", "Overwatch"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which game has Buyback?",
      "answers": ["Dota 2", "LoL", "CS:GO"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
